mommysavers.com 2011-06-18

# Privacy Policy | Mommysavers.com

**Privacy Policy  
**At Womensforum.com, we respect the privacy of the viewers who visit our communities and share their personal information with us. So we’ve designed our site and programs with their privacy in mind. Our Privacy Policy describes how we obtain, use and disclose non-public personal information about our viewers to our select marketing partners. You will be subject to the terms of this Policy if you register with us or use any of our services.

This Privacy Policy is subject to change.

**Customer Profile Protection**

**Information about All Visitors  
**Unless otherwise noted in special promotions, Womensforum.com generally gathers information about its users collectively and only uses this data to determine how to improve the overall experience for our visitors and members. If this information is shared with our partners or sponsors, it is only in the aggregate, which enables them to better understand how Womensforum.com visitors use and enjoy our site and which resources are of primary interest to them.

**Advertising  
**We may release subscriber data to responsible third parties for marketing purposes. Womensforum.com uses several third parity ad-serving companies to serve and monitor the advertisements that you see on our Web site. If you would like to know more about the information gathering practices and “opt-out” procedures of our third-party ad servers, please contact us at support@Womensforum.com This e-mail address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it .

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

**Research  
**Womensforum.com may research our users’ demographics, interests and behavior based on the information provided to us upon registration. We may do this to better understand and serve our visitors. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. Womensforum.com may share this aggregated data with select marketing partners.

**Specific Information about You  
**In the Registration section of Womensforum.com, you will be asked for some personal information, including; email address, password, first name, zip code, gender and year of birth. We may also request optional information including; last name, postal address, marital status, children, annual household income and special interests. This information is stored in a secure database and is used only as described above.

**Information Usage  
**In order to provide you with exemplary services, products, and the benefits of our selected partnerships, Womensforum.com displays multiple forms of advertisements from select partners. By better knowing our viewers, we are able to more effectively target content and sponsors offers to our viewers.

Womensforum.com uses an opt-in system before sharing user information with anyone. You always have the option of not providing permission for your information to be shared. If you do not wish to allow your data to be shared, you can choose not to use a particular service or not to participate in certain promotions or contests.

**Surveys, Promotions and Special Offer Goods and Services  
**We may seek information from you from time to time in connection with surveys, contests, promotions or special offers on sponsor goods and services. Participation in these activities is completely voluntary. The information requested may include contact information (such as name and address), demographic information (such as age and income level), preferences and interests.

You may have the opportunity to receive materials or special offers from third parties. If you choose to opt-in to receive information from these third parties, Womensforum.com may share your name and e-mail address with them.

**Links  
**Partners and merchants listed in womensforum.com have separate privacy policies and data collection practices. We encourage you to read the privacy statement of every Web site that collects personally identifiable information about you. When you click on an ad of a third-party linked to our site, for example, you may leave Womensforum.com and will be interacting directly with the third-party. That party may collect and use information about you in a way that is different from us. Although the third-party will not receive personally identifiable information about you from us (without your consent), it may know that you meet the criteria it sets for the distribution of its offers on our site.

**Third Party Data and Aggregated Data  
**Womensforum.com may disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes.

**Third Party Advertising  
**We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please contact us at support@Womensforum.com This e-mail address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it .

NAI Opt Out of Behavioural Advertising

The NAI Opt-out Tool was developed in conjunction with our members for the express purpose of allowing consumers to “opt out” of the behavioural advertising delivered by our member companies. [Please click here for further information](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Third Party Cookies  
**In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

**Children  
**We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and feel strongly about protecting the rights and privacy of children. As such, we do not collect or use any personal information from children we know to be under the age of 13, and will remove personally identifying information about such minors from our system. We are compliant with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) of 1998. [See this page for more information](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/buspubs/coppa.htm).

**Membership Cancellation  
**Our members have the option of cancelling their membership with Womensforum.com at any time by sending an email to unsubscribeme@Womensforum.com This e-mail address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it .

**Your IP Address  
**We may note your IP address when you visit our site. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer our web site, track user movements and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We collect aggregate (anonymous) information on persons who access our site so that we can keep it up-to-date, useful and relevant to visitors.

**Cookies  
**“Cookies” are files with information that is stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Womensforum.com uses cookies only to keep track of user I.D. information.

**Disclosure of Information  
**Womensforum.com may disclose information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our terms of use or causing injury to, or interfering with, our rights, property, other users, or anyone else.

Womensforum.com may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our service to you.

**Your Consent  
**By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Womensforum.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the revised policy on this page so that you are always aware of any changes.

**Security Precautions  
**Your Womensforum.com account is password protected. Only you have access to your personal information. Cautiously guard your password.

**Disclaimer  
**Please be aware that no data transmitted over the Internet is guaranteed to be 100% secure. Thus, Womensforum.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or information that is transmitted to you from our products, services or partners. Sometimes the information you disclose can be collected and used by others. If you post personal information that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.
